Oh
Hey guys
That idiot doesn't know how to run a podcast hold on you guys run it like I gotta take it all really quick
What up? What up? What up? What up? What up? What up good time we in here?
What up? What up?
There you go.
She said she got to take Paul. Shout out to the chat.
That was the most retarded stream I ever joined in my entire life.
But I don't know it's a lot going on people don't know who kicking who knew and me
I know I know for a fact DJ electric muted all of us, but she wanted to talk to you
I guess you think she's not that it's your fault, you know, but she thought she you know, I guess
She thinks that's her platform. I don't know, you know, that should not cool though
But it was DJ electric that put you back that that put everybody back stage unless you think he lying for he lies he lies
He lies
I'll be this kid he's stream
fucking
What's his name
Psyche lies he lies
Yeah, because I'll tell you this if she did that he could have brought us right back in right he can maneuver it
Yeah, he lies
And that's what I don't like is that he uses people and then like he will like use people as a pedestal and when he's done
He'd like I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything. No it happened like that like he lies. He lies and I'll explain to you guys later on
He's a liar liar. I'll explain the big pipe situation all that but
So why is DJ lecture saying that he has Alex at the as an admin? Do you believe
Because she says that he has a few people as admins, but he said he only has her
so I don't know if Alex would be an admin but I know for a fact for a fact and I have messages
from him asking me over and over to be his admin and I told him I don't want the responsibility
I know how it goes I'm gonna get blamed for shit he goes no one has to know you can do a ghost
you can be my ghost admin no one will know right and I said no that sounds like that sounds like some
psychopathic manipulation well that's what it is it's like that person will
have to keep a secret you both have to keep a secret and then meanwhile you're
gonna deny that shit is happening because I know the night that I try to
join on DJ Electra wasn't even around and he's saying it was him
So why was he letting other people on?
And he wasn't there, he was asked out, he was sleeping.
It's all bullshit.
Whether he's drinking or confusing shit, I don't think so.
I think I'm definitely the fool.
And like he said, he's evil and I'm the fool.
I am.
No, no, let's say.
I've never, I've never liked my drawing because I just wanted to see what I was going on.
I've never been on Psyche as well.
I wanted to see what was going on over there. That was a very...
And then she tried to make people feel like guilt trip them by saying I'm a band myself and chat. I'm a kick myself
I'm a band myself and and string yard is that I'm like girl like she said it two times
I ain't say shit then she said that shit again. I'm like bitch if you all leave just leave I try to be a
She's trying to give her, you know, psyche, psyche,
so she can hear psyche.
Yeah, so she can hear psyche, tell her, no, no, no, no,
don't do, don't do this.
I understand that she helped them save that channel.
Cool, thank you.
But you don't gotta use that to, you know,
have some type of power over his channel.
And psyche won't say shit to her.
Psyche won't say shit to her.
She can mute people, she can kick people,
bring people back up, but he won't say shit to her.
That's it, not cool.
And all fairness I've talked to her many times. I do think she was drinking today. It was
I mean, I do not everybody but what I'm
What I'm trying to tell you is that I've done the same thing where I'm like, I don't want to just
unmod me. I don't want to be here anymore because you legit feel like the pressure of you being
attacked while psyche does nothing. He'll go backstage and he needs to be like, you know what?
No, guys. Listen, I'll be honest with you. Sorry to interrupt what you're saying. I know you're mad.
You know what?
Sometimes I actually was gonna title that today. I was gonna title that. I think he's extremely fake and I
Really think he's up to no good, but I'm tired of that fucking bullshit
Well, I'd rather talk to you than him because guess what I don't listen here and I careless Kate can be in here
Um, I don't bound anybody if anybody banned person
Confess now your sins. I don't know why person would be banned
Arthur, I don't know what you're trying to instigate, but you know, just calm down right now
I
Will explain the whole situation where I got set off
It was so bad. Let's see when someone dreams because he's kind of my witness on what happened the following morning
I get along with same engine same issue. Joy. Hi, Narkal. Hey juice. Hey everybody
To not a minute. Yes little hell belly drone
Marcy hey, hey
All right easy and I never heard her I've never had an interaction where she was
sounding the way she was sounding today so she was definitely tipsy I don't
know her so that's first time I've ever talked to that woman I don't know who she
is let's put this into perspective okay
DT Electra made an intro video for Psyche. She took bullets for him. I know I know that she
What she did was you know, the whole control thing like okay
I'm gonna remove this this and this and that but he's gotta appreciate the people that have been there for him
I'm done shit for him and he doesn't have to make her do the dirty work
Go to college for psychology or something
Who me yes
People way faster than you can because you study psychology doesn't mean you're a psychic
No, no psychology is is knowing people's minds
Well, see that's the thing like let's say you're a psychologist, which I'm not I only have you know
I say psychology have a bachelor's and I wasn't trying to be a therapist. I wasn't doing clinical psychology
I was doing research. So it's a whole different scene. I
Calculation I deal with math and logic
But even like if you were doing clinical psychology as a therapist each person that comes in is a new person
and you can't just look at them and be like I know everything you get to know them and then you slowly learn about their behavior, right?
No, I'll agree with that. Sure. Why not? Yeah
Yeah, so Eldo, I would say because I know that you you really I've done this too where I want to give
Psyche excuses over and over and be like oh because it's like that
But no he's the one in charge put yourself in the same situation if I was your admin if I was your admin
Okay, and I'm fucking around. Let's say if she was fucking around. What would you do? You would be like be that stop playing
Stop playing right?
Yes, yes, I'm like look don't just
Band people because you need to speak don't you know mute people? You know because you need to you know really
It's only if the person isn't there, but psych is fucking right there. He's there, you know
Just because he kicks himself off screen does not mean he's not there. We know he's still there so
He definitely needs to take control of that shit.
Yeah, he's back, he's back, hey.
I think he is a fake ass motherfucker.
I agree.
All right.
You know, can I ask you a question, Aldo?
Yeah
He say that it was was that her that was admitting that she was putting she put me backstage
Or was that site? No, she was already gone. She was she was already
I mean, nah, but why would he lie on her because she can always come back and say, no, it wasn't so
That's why I believe psyche because why lie on a situation where she can come back home panel the next day and say
No, it wasn't me. Why are you saying you know what I'm saying? So that's why I had to ask and that's why I believe them because it's like
While I don't a person that's still here. They're not late. You know, I'm saying they're gonna fucking defend
You would know you would figure it out
I
Life I hate
Liars. Yeah, I read Samantha. I didn't threaten him first of all if he called that a threat
But I know for a fact it was him because as soon as I would speak about psyche
You know why I know it's him
DJ Electra sat there and me and her went back and forth
She even called me a bitch and I was like what the fuck this and that as soon as I said something about psyche
And what he did to me that night was fucking mr. Big Pies
He put me backstage and I was discussing about how he was asking for money
Well, he is definitely a liar and he's dishonest.
I'll say that.
Yes, and I know Eldor has like this like soft spot. I do too. I do too psyche
No, I'm saying he doesn't get it
He doesn't get it like Eldor wants to be like well, that's what happened because like somebody said it
No, I fell for that bullshit all the time where I would be like you just did that to me
And then we would talk and be like beta beta. Yeah, I didn't need I didn't know I wasn't even there
I didn't I didn't even know I'll give you the LD 15 example. Okay?
He led LB up and this is not the last time. It was like two weeks ago and I messaged him
I said are you fucking serious? He goes? Oh, I know I just kicked him
Um, I ended my life because I like this and that he has this awkwardness
He just sits there and doesn't say anything. Hold on you guys. Let's get true stone in there. I'm sorry not to laugh
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing about
How people don't realize that the Syke guy is a fucking nut job
Truth don't is it you?
They something so I don't I just make sure
Are you gonna get poor mom?
No, he doesn't form on me. Maybe he's working on
Yeah, but he just joined why he wouldn't say nothing
I think I think it might have not been him because somebody else like under the name of sake also try to join and
Then they left
To poor mommy last night
Yeah
Who should me yeah, he's right there
No, listen psyche are you fucking serious that you fucking are gonna blame me being put backstage on DJ Electra
Don't know what happened. I don't know what happened. You don't know what happened. You don't know what happened again. You were confused
I'm drunk. I forgot. I don't know. I don't know what happened
You need to be honest with people look at a smile you guys look at who is the fool, right?
Fool
No, let's say people could tell when people are not honest. I know. I know
You know how many women have left your panel and were hurt crying. I don't care. I know your cats are adorable
I'm talking to you right now. Okay. I know I know Lola is beautiful. I know
And that's how you got me with your fucking cute cats. Okay. Now. Let's talk
Yeah, I say something and then you guys
Shaved his face he looked like agent Smith from the matrix
It's not but he mad get it come on. That's it. That's all I had to say he meant so I'm gonna I'm gonna name some people tiger butterfly
Okay, I've text message from her talking and talking with her. Okay. Go ahead. Yeah. Why won't she come back?
You know what you did?
Because she was so drunk because she was so drunk
But you never drink you're so sober
But no, I know
Backsager did DJ electric that because I know the truth when I was addressing you about mr. Big Pipe
We have a deputy backstage then
It was like 15 minutes ago
Hey, man, I don't I don't know where you know, but you I heard you say I heard you say something like oh, I'm gonna
I'm sorry alive now. I'm gonna I'm gonna cook you and then so you put me back say so elder
Did you hear that? It wasn't DJ Electra. It's ready. What does that threaten? I was ready though. Are you listening?
Damn, what the heck? You told me that it was DJ Lecture that put it up.
Don't tell me lies, and that's not a threat.
If I say that I'm gonna go live, and I'm gonna fuck you,
because you were cheating me, you were cheating me, that's not a threat.
You see the lies you see it. Yeah, wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
Don't remember
I don't know if there's a delay when he's talking I don't I don't trust this guy. I think he's a he's a
No, it's like he needs to accept responsibility. I am gonna fucking talk about him all fucking day long until he just he knows
Everything everything
You're quiet right now. You're quiet right now, but you're seeing the truth, right? You hear the truth
I mean, I, I, I, I, I, I think, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I
Over and over
Mike messing up again, so yeah, do whatever you did last time to fix it
Yeah, she's gonna come back I just
Got scared for a second. I was like
Hey, bro, I'm getting cave on a hyperlite. Oh, dude. So you know the reason it's my cheeks
I joined us cuz I had
Customary in my chat and she said I'm gonna go join
psychs
podcast and
People are saying my child like you just kept her backstage all the time. Yeah, let her join
Okay
Just for 30 seconds
Electra has put all the women backstage today beta. She did say she did put you backstage now
I don't know if it's the specific time you're talking about
But she has dropped every woman up there on that panel backstage today
Christine, I understand that I know you on, um,
T.J. Electra probably, you know, didn't start on the right foot or whatever that's going on,
but Psyche just admitted that he put me backstage because I threatened to go live on him.
Yeah, and that's what I said. I know that you ended up in back a couple of times.
He said he don't remember. He said he don't remember.
He doesn't remember.
I want to say something.
I have never had a problem with DJ Electra until today.
I don't even know who that is.
Okay, I didn't even know. I have no idea.
I have spoken to her because, you know, she's a nurse. I'm a nurse.
Yeah, I do.
And even this morning,
even this morning, her and I were talking until I went back and listened to a few things,
and then her slurring her words and then going after every single woman in chat.
Christine, you are a very intelligent woman.
You know how to analyze and understand things.
If she is not, if she's drinking,
who do you think is the pilot?
Who is the channel host?
When he's there, who should be taking control?
Well,
but i'm gonna tell you because i'm i admin summers and summers there but she may not
be paying attention because she knows i'm there so i will take control over it
let's forget about that situation can we rewind back to two nights ago sorry mr good
like let mr big pipes call me a predator twice and when i you even stood up for me
What did he do? Again, he said, um, I don't know. I need money.
Come on, how many excuses are we going to make for
one of the three hundred hours?
He needs to fucking have a backbone and stand up and no,
one moment, you weren't there.
Psychic, you went up to you went up to three hundred dollars
and kept putting Vita in the back and I know.
And you even said it was a joke when somebody called me a predator.
No, but Vita, it was it was so ridiculous.
that. Yeah, somebody called you that on my fucking panel. I wouldn't laugh about it and I wouldn't
backstage you. I'm backstage now. The other day they were in your chat, everyone's saying.
When you let him come back and laugh it off and the next day, Kamen was there and he laughed
at it again. It's not joke. It doesn't. Okay, beautiful. I'm in second.
I
Mr. Terrell doesn't matter it's always said in your chat you and Bita have a personal relationship
You need to stick up for her just like
Like Bita are you okay? I was crying
I even cried today because of what was said, because the way psyche treated me, because I love you and I care about you.
You know who you check on me? Tracy, Paige, DJ Alexia, and Christine. I'm sure you would too if you had my contacts.
This man never gave a fuck about me.
Beada.
You're overreacting. Okay, beat it.
I don't think you're overreacting.
It's not a fucking joke.
It's not a suck-a-logically manipulator.
Everybody can see what you're doing, dude.
He is reacting, not overreacting.
People can see right through you.
In one moment, DJ Ledger, I hope you're listening.
You're a fucking liar.
Because we're not talking behind his back, bitch.
But good times. What are you piping up your piping in you have something to say? I'm I'm saying you you think you can manipulate people
Oh, please please
One more one person agrees with you it's true
What you know, you know, Mr. Big Pies, you know what he was you know how it even started while you call me a predator
No, all I did was tell him let other because he was like all about me me me
I'm me me me people are like and I said can you let other people talk because it was God he's worth it
He goes you predator lady
Why do you even take him seriously nobody you were there nobody can you please please one time?
I know you take the link sometime
Come up here and tell me am I fucking wrong?
Am I fucking delusional?
But site you can apologize, but the actions have to follow
And then we can talk now
Yeah, that's how it should be done. Yeah, I should be caught. Yeah, I shouldn't be on the panel. You should be talking to each other
You did what did you do you have mr. Big Pipe over there playing his black music talking about
25 years ago showing pictures of them. She doesn't like maybe they don't want their pictures show
Mr. Big Pipe's is 40 and he's showing pictures of girls what he was with like in high school
Okay. He's a fucking creep. There's a reason. Well, people tell you
I know you're angry and you're trying to spit your shit out
fucking um, like
Last year he was trying to hook up with like a 18 year old girl
Well, I mean, I mean, you know, do you know cinnamon toast can I cinnamon toast can he goes he's a streamer
He goes, uh, he's kind of famous
It's always dick before chicks with Psyche though. Oh
Fucking clumsy flamboyant. I whatever her name is. I want clairvoyant. I want tiger butterfly
I want all these fucking people that you can't on over fucking men to come and talk. Okay. No, no, beta
Let's do a roll call. Let's make sure it's it's Amanda. It's me. Okay. It's Amanda. We got Amanda. We got pearl. Okay, everybody's safe.
Bita, I was up there with you, honey. When it went down, you may not remember, but I was on panel with you and I told pipes he needed to apologize.
What does psyche do he's like he laughs like it's not a big deal like he's a liar
Pathological liar, which is why I wanted to get dropped. That's usually a sign of a psychopath or a sociopath. Okay. Let's let's stop
No, we don't we don't be honest
like people that
The next morning salmon came up I came up we were talking and he just started laughing and smirking again
And he just went on and sucking cheeks to me
You know, he's doing it on purpose and you know, I know you think that I'm like somebody that I love you
And I'll come back but
Psyche I'm fucking a bitch. Okay. I'm a
Christine oh my god, I am so sorry. I'm just telling you guys if anybody is doing anything
Something about cancer with the how about the cancer Amanda
I don't know what's going on but I remember me, you and Rain spoke and this was way later huh, this was way later and life left me and ex out on the panel and I was like, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on, I don't know what's going on,
And we got an argument because he tried to lie and say that wasn't
Hold on let the man talk please
Anyway, JT argued with me said it wasn't you want more pictures
And then
Let me like sweetheart Amanda, I will give you I'll tell you this what happened with you rain JT, whatever
That should have been psyche's job to moderate that even though I did it
You know with you and rain. I'm glad we had great results when JT was doing that. Who should be paying attention is the fucking panel host
Listen, don't do that. I'm gonna fucking ban you. That's my issue with him
I think he's a pathological liar and the thing about pathological liars
They think they're smart. What do you go? Did he leave Mike checking in?
Yeah, he always leaves. He always leaves when, um, you know, I want to say something.
He always leaves. He always leaves. Salman was there. And let's make sure it's him
the next morning after the home of their big pipes. Send me. What are you doing?
Let's make sure it's him, Salman. There's me. What's up, Salman?
Yeah
Do you remember the next morning
Like mr. Big price what it's like he do he just laughs. He's like it's not a big deal
He just
I see you
Oh
It was DJ electric
Liar
Like why you get mad I asked him a question and then I repeated what he said that's all I did
He's a bad
Drunk ass you don't say that 50 times already such a drunk ass
The show face get the fuck out of it
Enjoy your blue
Wow, none of you will turn your camera on you're making fun of me for you look crazy with you
You look crazy with your camera on you need to turn that shit off good times. Oh come on turn your camera off
How about I show my dick
With bad pipes peeing in a bottle on on street
That's disgusting and he stands up and does it right on the street. You want to do it good times won't do it
You know, I just like to try to fuck you.
And these look, listen, bro, listen to me.
No, kiss my cheeks.
Calm down, baby.
I know those kids.
I remember those kids.
They will bite themselves and wear those fucking helmets back in the day.
These these niggas growing.
They growing up now.
These are the niggas on these panels now.
Full blown retarded.
Come on.
No, I'm not.
No, you stupid.
Full blown retarded.
Ain't no come on nothing. Let's just be honest and be real
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Christine, the thing is like you and DJ Electra could have been resolved is like he intervened, he does need to intervene, he needs to be like, but he was walking and doing things and DJ Electra, he always does that, he finds the perfect opportunity to do that.
Well, I don't understand why she put me in back, I did nothing.
I didn't do anything either and he put me backstage and he just admitted it. So it's a lot of confusion and imagine
Christine, so you're gonna be an admin for him. It is gonna be your good
He's gonna throw you under the bus. Oh, I'm not being an admin for him. I'm saying imagine imagine
Yeah, yeah, well, that's why I was like, no, thank you
But here's the thing that I saw today and this was before you came on
She, DJ, was the one controlling everything and I'm sorry as an admin to somebody else's
stream yard.
You do not admin with your feelings, and trust me there are times on summers when when she's even there
And I so much want to remove these people and I never do it. There are some people. I can't stand
They come up on panel and I never do it because it's not about me and I can't do my
Christine I only have
One mod and it's
You only got one nigga watching your channel
He has more stuff than all of us he had he just lost it
All he got my chill newton
All these swatted me all these swatted me. I had a goddamn cops trying to kick my door. Do you know there's a law now against that?
Well
The one cop knew who I was he was laughing
Listen what site go man like I said a long time ago sites the first nigga to be homeless inside the house man
They picked that nigga before skin road and put that nigga in apartment. That's why
Good times, man, you got a sheet hanging over your door. You drunk
You watch your mouth, huh? No, you want to play that game with me?
No, no, no, no, he wanted to play the rotating circle dance game on putting backstage you couldn't disrespect me
Okay, be the lamb talk, though. We can't eat. We're eating. We're eating. We're eating. Come on. It's a joke.
Okay, we're eating. What's up, man?
I heard from someone, I heard from someone that you were nodded out on like drugs or something, and then they, there was a wellness check, not a swaddle.
You know what? I woke up at 5 a.m. and I went out. I mowed my grass and fucking did a bus yard and work out.
Hi, yo, yo. Why are you back at AB, though?
I don't want to talk about good times.
I don't care.
I fucking was tired.
I just fell asleep.
It's not about good times.
It's about sight.
Hey, can we let Si talk, please?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Si, go ahead.
Well, thank you.
Well, I just heard, like, you know, I've had a wellness check done, and it's like,
and the cops come and they'll say our backstab beta.
White backstab beta.
Go ahead.
I love you. I would have asked to be I love you. Why do you allow DJ Electra also do the same thing?
Why would you let Mr. Big Pipe call me predator and like play like
Harmonica and fucking stupid banji whatever the
Guitar and go la la put them on the big
And not
You fucking dick righty. Yeah, I get what he ever donates you
He's doing it five memberships, and I think he donated money was
Just calm down for a second
Go ahead, be the cook.
You lied, you lied.
Oh, Saman, stop it, stop it.
I didn't lie.
Wait, Saman was on the panel with you,
and we both were like, why would you let that happen?
And you just laughed, and you're like, it's just a joke.
So if somebody calls you a predator, you think it's funny.
No, I know people say that in your chat,
Yeah
Okay, what do you say
What do you say to the first the first thing he said to me the first time he was on your show with me
What did I do I take you off all the time no you did I left I left and I came back
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What does he call his a stupid shit? I can't go up like ten times a night
Shit, and I don't take your apology because you know what if you were really sincerely like you know
uh apologizing to me you would understand i'm not a f***ing predator and you wouldn't be able to say it
quite and then when he came on he's like oh she sounds like a homeless lady you know he knows
he knows me and exactly who i am he was on me all the time oh your version oh give it a whole
iranian f***ing history mr bigpipes is the biggest f***ing simp you'll step on a f***ing man woman
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
If somebody called me homeless, maybe, but if somebody called me a predator, that's not funny.
That's not funny.
If he actually put his name properly, it's like...
Good times, shout out.
Yeah, that's exactly what he prefers.
on the fucking stage when they're mostly men he will let them get away with every fucking thing
he will let them like just oh he put like one-on-one you want flirty diamond you want page here
suave her you know it's a fucking history he's a weirdo if he wasn't he wouldn't be on the internet
Oh my god
One time when I called you I said why did you end your life? Yeah, what'd you say?
Well, okay, I said I said I said LD is trying to come up at the end of the live because actually D. Hi
Was like saying like he's a
You're a liar. Hold on shut up the time shut up
You remember what you have the messages you said LD try to join and
You know
Whatever, I just didn't want them on and I told you all you got to do is either ignore them backstage or just say hey LD
I see you're trying to join.
I don't want you on my panel and that, and then that ended.
You're like, yeah, he's weird.
He's weird.
He just is awkward.
He does nothing.
Anyways, then comes like five days later,
you let him on the panel,
cause he had just nothing on except for fucking boxers.
And you were like,
was like shake I wrote in the chat shaking my fucking head and then I was like I just left
I took I just left and now you're like oh sat there and let him up there for the whole hour
and a half while he does nothing as usual. I don't want to say too much because I don't want to talk about this with me.
I can't see you in your boxers. I would say that can you see you're a crazy sociopath fucking
Pathopathological liar, and you probably keep talking about you want to see my
See that
Fuck fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you
Okay, okay
All kinds of fucking shit, bitch you're this this and that you fool scream me when I actually came out I was changing my underwear you
I blame myself
I am not going to be called a predator
Any kind of like jackass are weird predator is pretty bad pretty bad
Well, you know, he called you a filthy motherfucker and gave you the finger.
I've taken it.
Oh, I've heard this one customer.
You know, I think you like I have a hundred over you.
Be the dick over friends.
You heard what?
I didn't say she takes the finger.
You don't have to think.
No, customer.
You was I thought Bita just said you'd like to take the finger.
I
Somebody give me a finger
Prison for the rest of my life
Yes, I okay Schmeli. I'll give you a okay Schmeli. That's a really really good good comment
I will tell you what happened with me and Arthur.
He came up here, he said some things to me
that I thought were inappropriate and I said something,
but you know what?
I apologized and so did he.
It was addressed quicker than what's been happening
with me and Psyche.
And done with, yes.
But you know what? He said things to me. He was like your, you know, uncle, and I was like, you sound like a whatever.
And he apologized and we moved on. That's the difference.
By the way, me and Arthur are not friends. He doesn't have my number. He can't call me. He can't text me.
Psyche hasn't done any of that. So me and Arthur resulted in the long run way faster than Psyche could have.
It's about respect. It's about taking accountability. I took it. Other people can psyche will make excuses all fucking day long
The signs is right you're a narcissist
No, no, let's say pathological liars. They think they're smart and everybody else and they think they can just lie their way out of fucking conversations
I get reminded because I see people in the
Hell and she came back and she was there for you
Okay, yeah, great. They have just called me a big ego team
The elder you're in the line
Do you hear the lie?
What do you lie? What do you lie about?
He just made up the story right now in front of us.
Two of them. Two.
What did you say, Sike?
I didn't even tell you what I was going to say.
You said it like 10 seconds ago.
Why are you freaking out, homo?
Fucking fact.
You know what's that again, you know you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're you're
I think I actually saw a couple of people call you that and you just let it go by last night.
T you say black RG you're a mod if I can't screw psyche
That's what he says like
You're not it's a screw psyche. Okay. Okay. I don't know
Mutual mods who gives the fuck you're gonna threaten to take his mom cuz he just agreed with me first
He's gonna screw me just screw me
You're fucking mouth-hold
What?
Yeah, it's on the stick in your ear. Oh black card G. I'll remind you. I'll get on the computer
Jesus, I forget I keep forgetting my channel is
You're talking like a drunk. I mean, I had like I'm talking like a drunk
You know what? You're the one that forgets everything that you just lied about have a conversation. You what are you talking about psyche?
What is she talking about psyche? You're smart everybody
Don't know
Do you take your smile and everybody times in the dream?
Do you take your smile and everyone?
Jesus Christ this guy's fucking nuts
right. Are you? Are you sorry? Are you genuinely sorry? Are you genuinely sorry about? Yeah. Yeah.
How are you going to, what are you going to do with Mr. Big Pipes? I'm going to
Okay, he can go take a bit. He's gonna take a mr. Big poops. Well, I don't care
No, no, no when he joins are you gonna let him like harass women be rude? No, no, no
He has he has one more warning
So he gets one more chance
Yeah, well, we'll see
No, no, you will see
I
Read that one more warning by the way, that means
Because he has a dick and imagine liking mr. Big Pies dick and his music
You're you like weirdos you're
Fucking let her you get good times out of here. I want I want to hear beat us rust the shit out of you cuz you can't
You'll leave eventually
Trust me, he's gonna leave eventually he's getting to that point trust me
Good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good times, good
I already spoke, I already spoke to SIG on Discord.
Well, I saw you try to join,
but I'm going to tell you one thing that Carl said,
and he was on my panel,
so I'm not hiding it.
He says psyche is no good.
What? Good times.
Can you tell us, like,
are you still using a bedpan?
What's up with that?
Damn, Carl, if you listen and come back up here, Carl, you need to address this psyche
situation.
Right.
Beto, why would Carl say that about psyche?
Do you know?
Because he's a better tarot card reader.
He actually fucking did all the shit that psyche is doing and monetizing off of.
And he called it from like he got mad.
What?
Ragequad, Ragequad.
That guy is a pathological liar.
You know that, right?
Stop the fuck up, you fucking scum.
Carol, a scamming card reader.
I'm on your neck, good times.
He's a pathological reader.
Bita, you saying you're psyching the scammer?
Bita, are you saying you're psyching the scammer?
When he asked for $300 for fucking, like, you know.
What?
He just said, like, he just...
You got a good time. I'm on your neck. She fucking had
You threaten me it doesn't matter
Straighten you ain't gonna do shit. You're gonna die out of the way. You fucking old piece of shit
Oh, really? Are we gonna play this game?
You wanna play games, asshole?
Oh, Beena!
There you go, Beena. Look at that.
What do you do? What do you do?
He showed a stupid like
Taser BB gun, but I'm gonna what he showed. I'm not gonna let him be on the panel to show you any
You've been water gun. Okay. What a scumbag, huh?
Yeah, he's an asshole. Yeah, it was it was just like a fucking stupid like whatever that probably doesn't he know
You're welcome
Yeah, you're not gonna run anybody even time you fucking make it and minecraft you're not gonna fucking turn anybody good time
All right
Do it on your own?
Arthur Arthur fucking grilled him and he fucking did that come on good time fucking pussy
Bitch me
Beta yes
Oh, yeah, he bit me for that man.
It was a beating on you guys.
I had the same one.
It looks like a real one.
He tries to shoot raccoons with it and he can't get anywhere.
And, um, is he like idiot?
That's awesome.
Do it again.
And I swear to God, I will come after your channel.
So he's gonna do it.
He's gonna do it.
I will fucking come after your channel.
So fucking hard.
You wouldn't even fucking be able to sleep at night.
Okay.
Yeah.
I wouldn't risk it though.
And I will tell Crystal Marie
that he's never ever to join your panel.
Give me a beat up.
I think you should add it.
He's backstage and he's like smoking a cigarette
or like trying to like, you know,
act like he's all cool about this.
Some people are going to believe this shit
and just stop it. Okay.
You're going to over what, Arthur?
Dummy?
Yo, Vito, my boss started over money guys patient down with home seventy-two hours yesterday with a lighter a lighter gun
And it showed playing so just restart it we start
Thank you